CONNIE ROSENDALE

07506580312 | connie.rosendale@gmail.com

PROFILE

As a hands on learner, I started my career with an apprenticeship rather than a degree. This has given me over three years experience, progressing through roles at a large publishing company. My key skills are HTML5, CSS3 and jQuery; with a keen eye for design and an interest in all aspects of user experience.

EXPERIENCE

UI DEVELOPER, INCISIVE MEDIA; LONDON - 2016 - PRESENT

Working as part of the web team, this role allows me to review and improve the user experience of both our websites and apps. My focus is mainly on apps and subscription microsites, this includes migrating over 30 apps to a new and improved platform which significantly improved the user experience of the end product.

JUNIOR WEB PRODUCER, INCISIVE MEDIA - 2014 - 2016

As a member of a small team, I was responsible for creating webpages, updating CSS and Javascript files and setting up apps in iTunes and Google Play. My main project during this time was creating 8+ subscription microsites for our brands, using Wordpress. This process included research, user testing, child theme creation and training marketing teams on Wordpress.

DIGITAL APPRENTICE, INCISIVE MEDIA - 2013 - 2014

Starting my career as a digital apprentice allowed me to work with many different departments, picking up a variety of skills. My main responsibilities during this time included updating CSS and Javascript files, creating print and web graphics and trafficking adverts through DFP.

EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS

- 10 GCSE's including an A for IT and A* for Business Studies
- ICT OCR National Diploma: Distinction (Equivalent to 2 A-levels grade A)
- Advanced Level Apprenticeship in IT, Software, Web & Telecoms Professionals
- Microsoft MTA: HTML5 Application Development Fundamentals

KEY SKILLS

- HTML5 & HTML; 5+ years experience
- CSS3 & CSS; 5+ years experience
- Javascript; 4+ years experience
- ¡Query; 3 years experience
- SASS & SCSS; 3 years experience
- Wordpress, 3+ years experience
- Illustrator; 3 years experience
- Photoshop; 5+ years experience

REFERENCES

Available on request.